

#### CONTACT

**PHONE** +4917664209354

# **EMAIL** franko.safradin13@gmail.com







#### **HARD SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- Sass
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Node.js
- React.js
- Next.js
- Git
- MongoDB
- Responsive Design

#### SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- Intercultural competences
- Presentation skills
- Self-marketing
- · Analitical thinking
- Flexibility
- Team building & team work
- SCRUM

#### LANGUAGE

- English (C1)
- German (B2)
- Croatian (Native)

### **FRANKO SAFRADIN**

#### WEB DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT ME**

Open-minded and hardworking person, currently located in Düsseldorf, always on the hunt for new knowledge, which will benefit me and the people around me. New to the development industry, but ready to learn from more experienced colleagues, and also to teach those who are less experienced than

#### **EDUCATION**

### DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH November 2021 - November 2022

- Enrolled into one-year long web development course
- Learned and studied technologies that enabled me to create full-stack applications
- Learned technologies (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node and MongoDB)
- Graduated a Bootcamp with final MERN project
- In-depth knowledge of soft skills
- Finished B2 German course

#### Studyon GmbH, Düsseldorf January 2021 - October 2021

• Finished B1.2 German course

#### WORKING EXPERIENCE

## Housekeeper InterContinental Düsseldorf | 12/2018-12/2020

- Supervised cleaning service workers
- · Provided high-end customer service
- · Control and ordering of hotel amenities
- Worked in fast paced, international, multicultural company

### Front Office/Receptionist Suncani Hvar d.d Hvar | 05/2017-08/2018

- · Working in the tourist resort
- Fulfilling guest wishes, providing high-end stay
- Sharpened my MS Office and Hotelsoftware skills